YOSRI BOUABID

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



Tunisia, Ben arous

yosribouabid@gmail.com

+21655384895

PROFILE

Full Stuck Web Developer, Recent graduated. Currently working in an internship as back-end developer, to establish my skills and abilities even more. Highly organized multitasking with expertise in scheduling projects, enhancing designs and verifying code.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Back-end Developer at Heroi 02/2022 - Currnet

- Developed and maintained an authentication API for the web site using Golang.
- Involved in DB design and writing the SQL scripts to create DB using PostgreSQL and MongoDB.
- Developed the Rest Services, and wrote the Unit testing for the application.
- Implemented robust security and data protection measures.
- Cooperated with front-end developers and other team members to design more cohesive and functional feature for the web site.

Full stack developer at 01/2022 - 02/2022 **Dope-Stickers**

Link

- Designing the front-end architecture and the UI using ReactJS, and ensuring a responsive design.
- Developed unit test cases for testing and automation.
- Developing the APIs for the back-end using NodeJS.
- · Creating servers and databases for functionality, while meeting both technical and consumer needs.

09/2021 - 10/2021 Mayday Academic project

Link

- Used NodeJS to implement a custom Restful API for the
- Accomplished the connection between React app and the
- Invoked React promises for asynchronous routing and calls to the Restful API.

LINKS

https://yosri-ctrl.github.io/Portfolio



https://github.com/Yosri-ctrl



https://www.linkedin.com/in/yosri-bouabid/ (in)

EDUCATION

Holberton school

01/2020 - 09/2021 | Full stack software engineer certificate.

Al-Olaya school

09/2014 - 06/2015 | Secondary school certificate.

SKILLS

- Golang
- React.js
- Node.js / JavaScript
- Python
- Java
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- Git / GitHub
- Docker

LANGUAGES

speaking, reading, writing English

French speaking, reading, writing

Arabic Native languge